It's raining!
Yağmur yağıyor!
Oh no
Eyvah,
Paimon forgot to bring an umbrella...
Paimon şemsiye getirmeyi unuttu...
Come on
Hadi,
Let's hurry before it rains harder!
yağmur şiddetlenmeden gidelim!
Ugh, it's raining again?
Of, yine mi yağmur?
I've had enough of this weather
Bu havadan gına geldi.
There go my travel plans...
Seyahat planım yalan oldu...
Did you read the news this morning?
Bu sabah haberleri okudun mu?
Quick
Çabuk,
Put away everything on the clotheslines!
askıdaki çamaşırları topla!
When is this rain going to stop...
Ne zaman bitecek bu yağmur...
Hydro Dragon, Hydro Dragon, don't cry!
Su Ejderhası, Su Ejderhası, lütfen ağlama!
They're planning to reanimate the monster...
Canavarı diriltmeyi planlıyorlar...
We have to report this to the Chief Justice
Bunu Başyargıca bildirmeliyiz.
The Fortress of Meropide...
Meropide Kalesi...
It's a good place for me
Benim için güzel bir yer.
He owes me so many answers...
Bana bir sürü cevap borçlu...
Neuvillette?
Neuvillette mi?
You could say he's the real symbol of Fontaine's justice
Onun Fontaine'de adaletin sembolü olduğu söylenebilir.
Watch him closely
Bir gözünüz onun üzerinde olsun.
He could be trouble
Başımıza dert açabilir.
How can two completely different species possibly coexist?
Tamamen farklı iki tür nasıl bir arada yaşayabilir ki?
Who's been threatening Melusines?
Melusinaları kim tehdit ediyormuş?
Show yourself!
Göstersin kendini!
You will see much
İnsan dünyasında
In the human world
neşeden kedere kadar
From the delightful to the depressing...
pek çok şey göreceksin...
And one day, when you have dwelt among humanity long enough
Ve bir gün, insanlar arasında yeterince yaşadıktan sonra
You will be placed to bring judgment over all
Fontaine'in geçmişinin sözcüsü olarak
As the spokesperson for Fontaine's past
herkese hüküm vermek üzere yerini alacaksın.
Good morning, Monsieur Neuvillette!
Günaydın Mösyö Neuvillette!
The rainy season's almost over...
Yağmur mevsimi bitmek üzere...
The skies are supposed to clear in a few days
Hava birkaç güne açacakmış.
I hope you find time to enjoy the sunny days ahead
Umarım güneşli günlerin tadını çıkarabilirsin.